{
    "subject": "resource/Hard_Boiled_(1919_film)",
    "predicate": "property/director",
    "object": "resource/Victor_Schertzinger",
    "human_readable": "The director of the 1919 film Hard Boiled is Victor Schertzinger.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9564322233200073,
            "question": "Who directed the 1919 film Hard Boiled?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.866805911064148,
            "question": "Is Victor Schertzinger known for directing other films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7343099117279053,
            "question": "Can you name another film directed by Victor Schertzinger?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4236438274383545,
            "question": "What year was the film Hard Boiled released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2633688151836395,
            "question": "What genre is the film Hard Boiled likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24849003553390503,
            "question": "Were there any famous actors who appeared in Hard Boiled?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2468433529138565,
            "question": "What were some common themes in films from 1919?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.042488861829042435,
            "question": "How has the perception of early cinema changed over time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.03237900510430336,
            "question": "How did filmmaking technology change between 1910 and 1920?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.017824387177824974,
            "question": "What impact did silent films have on popular culture?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The director of the 1919 film Hard Boiled is Victor Schertzinger.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3498_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did filmmaking technology change between 1910 and 1920?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3498_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has the perception of early cinema changed over time?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3498_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were some common themes in films from 1919?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3498_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3498_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3498_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3498_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3498_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3498_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3498_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3498_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3498_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3498_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3498_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, I will evaluate whether the statement \"The director of the 1919 film Hard Boiled is Victor Schertzinger.\" is supported by the documents.\n\nHere's my evaluation:\n\n* The first document mentions that \"Hard Boiled is a 1919 American comedy silent film directed by Victor Schertzinger...\"\n* The second document also mentions that \"Hard BoiledDirected byVictor Schertzinger\"\n* Both documents are about the same movie, Hard Boiled.\n* There is no conflicting information in any of the documents.\n\nTherefore, based on this analysis, I conclude that:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports that Victor Schertzinger was indeed the director of the 1919 film \"Hard Boiled.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}